The lovable hero from Anastasia is back!
Bartok the Magnificent is a animation, comedy,
family film directed by Gary Goldman.
Albino bat Bartok – former sidekick to the wicked Grigori Rasputin – ventures to prove his
true worth on a new quest to defeat the legendary Russian witch Baba Yaga.
Bartok (voice), played by Hank Azaria.
Zozi (voice), played by Kelsey Grammer.
Baba Yaga (voice), played by Andrea Martin.
Ludmilla (voice), played by Catherine O'Hara.
The Skull (voice), played by Tim Curry.
Piloff (voice), played by Jennifer Tilly.
Bartok the Magnificent is a 1999 American direct-to-video animated
adventure comedy film directed by Don Bluth and Gary Goldman.
It is a standalone spin-off to the 1997 film Anastasia, also directed by Bluth and Goldman,
with Hank Azaria reprising his role from Anastasia as Bartok, an albino bat.
The film shows Bartok as a con artist who has the
opportunity to become a true hero.
The film explores themes of witch, cartoon, prince, musical, bat.
The tone is lighthearted.